houseinthesun.com 2016-05-16

# Privacy Statement

### Privacy Statement

House in the sun Scandinavia AB is totally committed to protecting your privacy when you use our website, HouseInTheSun.com. This policy is to explain how and why we collect the information as a result of your initial enquiry, how we protect it, what we do with it and how you can manage our utilisation of your information or terminate usage.

Any questions regarding our Privacy Policy should be directed to contact at HouseInTheSun.com at info @ HouseInTheSun.com.

Changes to this privacy statement or use of data.

From time to time, we may add or change functions, features or services offered by advertisement online or offline and at our website. This, and our commitment to protecting the privacy of your personal information, may result in periodic changes to this privacy policy. As a result, please remember to refer back to this privacy policy regularly to review any amendments. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

Your consent and acceptance of these Privacy Statement terms.

By using any HouseInTheSun.com or our Services, you unconditionally agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy.

**Data collection and usage**

HouseInTheSun.com collects and processes information from your website visits, requests for services and phone calls in order to:

1\. Identify you each time you visit a website or wish to have a Service provided;

2\. Process and send requests by you, such as email updates

3\. Improve our Services and Website.

4\. Customise the information you receive from us via registration process, and which support any specific requests for information you may make through keyword searches;

5\. Send you information we think you may find useful, including information about new and existing my HouseInTheSun.com services, offers and newsletters.

6\. Compile customer testimonials that may be repeated on advertising material online or offline but without mention of your email or contact details.

**About registering with us for services**

In order to use some of our website services such as email updates, you must first complete the registration form online at our website or register with us over the telephone. During registration you are required to give their contact information (such as name and email address). This information is used to send you the information you requested about our services at the time of registration, as well as future

information about those same services and others offered by HouseInTheSun.com that could be of interest in the future.

You are under no obligation to provide all information, but if you choose not to provide certain details please be aware that that this may mean we are unable to provide you with certain services or to personalise/tailor our services for you (for example a newsletter).

**Security**

HouseInTheSun.com places a great importance on the security of all information associated with our customers. We have security measures in place to attempt to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of customer data under our control. While we cannot ensure or guarantee that loss, misuse or alteration of data will not occur, we use our best efforts to prevent this. 

**Use of Cookies**

Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to your hard drive to store and sometimes track information about you. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but if you prefer, you can change your browser to prevent that. However, you may not be able to take full advantage of a website if you do so. Cookies are specific to the server that created them and cannot be accessed by other servers, which means they cannot be used to track your movements around the web. Although they do identify a user's

computer, cookies do not personally identify customers or passwords. 

We use cookies for the following reasons:

1\. To identify who you are and to access your account information;

2\. To estimate our audience size and patterns;

3\. To ensure that you are not asked to register twice;

4\. To track preferences and to improve and update our website; and

5\. To track the progress and number of emails opened in some of our marketing communications.

**Content**

Please note that whilst we take every precaution to ensure that the details provided by our partners are correct, they are supplied to us and should be verified prior to an exchange of contract. These details do not constitute any part of an offer or contract, and no responsibility is accepted as to their accuracy, nor of statements made by ourselves concerning properties. We cannot be held responsible for any expenses incurred by applicants visiting properties which may have been let, sold or withdrawn. While we make a huge effort to reflect correct descriptions and prices, none of the information contained in any HouseInTheSun.com web page is warranted by any party. Users assume all liability for use of any information found.

Confirmation of information published in the website is the sole responsibility of the purchasing party. The developers and management companies set their own purchase price and deposit policies. It is the investor's responsibility to request and obtain a written notice of the refund and cancellation policy from the agent. HouseInTheSun.com is not responsible for the refund of reservation deposits, or other fees for any reason. You are advised to seek appropriate professional advice before making any decisions based on the information provided.

All agreements and contracts are direct from the agent and must be enforced as such regardless of whether HouseInTheSun.com refered the sale. There is no charge for our services throughout the purchasing procedure. We work only on monthly listing fee basis with our agents and private sellers. It is advisable to ask the selling agent to confirm the total costs/fees payable before purchasing a property.

**Shared information**

HouseInTheSun.com will not share, sell or rent your personal information to third parties. However, we may disclose your personal information to third party suppliers who provide services on our behalf, for instance financial or tax services providers but only if you have expressed interest for additional information in these two elements.

HouseInTheSun.com may disclose aggregate statistics about our sales, our website visitors and customers of our telephone services in order to describe our services to prospective partners, advertisers and other reputable third parties and for other lawful purposes, but these statistics will not include personally identifying information.

HouseInTheSun.com may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or if it believes that such action is necessary to protect and defend the rights, property or personal safety of HouseInTheSun.com and its website, visitors to the website and customers of our Services.

By using the services of HouseInTheSun.com, you agree to the terms and conditions in this disclaimer.

HouseInTheSun.com registered office:

Eksundsvägen 9, 605 97 Norrköping, Sweden
